Guide to the Fales Manuscript Collection circa 1700-2000 MSS.001
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Letter sized boxes, 47643
  - De la Mare, Walter (1873-1956): General Correspondence, 1909-1929; 51166 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - De la Mare, Walter (1873-1956): General Correspondence, 1929-1953; undated; 51165 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - De la Mare, Walter (1873-1956): to Clemens, Cyril; Barrows, Miss, 1931; 51164 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - De la Mare, Walter (1873-1956): to Fabes, Gilbert, 1928-1934; 51163 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - De la Mare, Walter (1873-1956): to Bull, King, undated; 51162 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - De la Mare, Walter (1873-1956): to Rogers, Arthur, 1923-1952; 51161 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - De la Mare, Walter (1873-1956): MS. Introduction to Dickens' The Cricket on the Hearth, undated; 51160 (Box 38, Folder 7a)
  - De la Mare, Walter (1873-1956): MS. Books, undated; 51159 (Box 38, Folder 7b)
  - De la Mare, Walter (1873-1956): MS. A Child Asleep, undated; 51158 (Box 38, Folder 7c)
  - De la Mare, Walter (1873-1956): MS. Physic, undated; 51157 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - De la Rame´e, Marie Louise (1839-1908) (Ouida, pseud.): 1 of 2, undated; 51156 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - De la Rame´e, Marie Louise (1839-1908) (Ouida, pseud.), undated; 51155 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - De la Roche, Mazo, undated; 51154 (Box 39, Folder 3a)
  - Dell, Ethel May, undated; 51153 (Box 39, Folder 3b)
  - Dell, Floyd, undated; 51152 (Box 39, Folder 3c)
  - Dell, Floyd: MS. The Rise and Fall of Greenwich Village [Love in Greenwich Village], undated; 51151 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - De Morgan, Mary, undated; 51150 (Box 39, Folder 5a)
  - De Morgan, William (1839-1917), undated; 51149 (Box 39, Folder 5b)
  - Denison, William Thomas, Sir (1804-1871), undated; 51148 (Box 39, Folder 6a)
  - Dennis, Charles Henry, undated; 51147 (Box 39, Folder 6b)
  - De Quincey, Thomas (1785-1859), undated; 51146 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Derby, Edward (Henry Stanley, 15th Earl of), undated; 51145 (Box 39, Folder 8a)
  - Derby, Frederick (Arthur Stanley, 16th Earl of), undated; 51144 (Box 39, Folder 8b)
  - Derleth, August William (1909-1971): to Weil, James, 1959-1962; 51143 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Derleth, August William (1909-1971): to Weil, James, 1963-1964; 51142 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Derleth, August William (1909-1971): to Weil, James, 1965-1971; 51141 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Deroulade, Paul, undated; 51140 (Box 39, Folder 12a)
  - Derounian, Arthur, undated; 51139 (Box 39, Folder 12b)
  - De Selincourt, Basil, undated; 51138 (Box 39, Folder 12c)
  - [Destouches, Louis Ferdinand: see Box 39.5], 1690-2000; 51137 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_ac4530ca4aca2686d6f228d4bcfda488)
  - Deutsch, Babette, undated; 51136 (Box 39, Folder 13a)
  - De Vere, Aubrey Thomas, undated; 51135 (Box 39, Folder 13b)
  - De Vere, Stephen Edward, Sir, undated; 51134 (Box 39, Folder 13c)
  - Dexter, Paul, undated; 51133 (Box 39, Folder 14a)
  - De Young, Charles, undated; 51132 (Box 39, Folder 14b)
  - Dibdin, Charles (1768-1833), undated; 51131 (Box 39, Folder 15a)
  - Dibdin, Thomas Frognall (1776-1847), undated; 51130 (Box 39, Folder 15b)
  - Dibdin, Thomas John (1771-1841) [picture removed to picture file], undated; 51129 (Box 39, Folder 15c)
  - Dicey, Albert V., undated; 51128 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - [Dickens, Charles: see Boxes 40-44], 1690-2000; 51127 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_866eb99be24f9dbfa5d3577f637c045c)
  - Destouches, Louis Ferdinand (1894-1961) (Louis-Ferdinand Ce´line, pseud.): D'un Chateau L'autre, undated; 51126 (Box 39.5, Folder 1)
  - Destouches, Louis Ferdinand (1894-1961) (Louis-Ferdinand Ce´line, pseud.): Entretiens avec le Professeur Y. [version I], undated; 51125 (Box 39.5, Folder 2)
  - Destouches, Louis Ferdinand (1894-1961) (Louis-Ferdinand Ce´line, pseud.): Entretiens avec le Professeur Y. [version II], undated; 51124 (Box 39.5, Folder 3)
  - Destouches, Louis Ferdinand (1894-1961) (Louis-Ferdinand Ce´line, pseud.): Entretiens avec le Professeur Y. [version III], undated; 51123 (Box 39.5, Folder 4)
  - Destouches, Louis Ferdinand (1894-1961) (Louis-Ferdinand Ce´line, pseud.): Entretiens avec le Professeur Y. [version IV], undated; 51122 (Box 39.5, Folder 5)
  - Destouches, Louis Ferdinand (1894-1961) (Louis-Ferdinand Ce´line, pseud.): Entretiens avec le Professeur Y. [version V], undated; 51121 (Box 39.5, Folder 6)
  - Destouches, Louis Ferdinand (1894-1961) (Louis-Ferdinand Ce´line, pseud.): Entretiens avec le Professeur Y. [version VI], undated; 51120 (Box 39.5, Folder 7)
  - Destouches, Louis Ferdinand (1894-1961) (Louis-Ferdinand Ce´line, pseud.): Entretiens avec le Professeur Y. [version VII], undated; 51119 (Box 39.5, Folder 8)
  - Destouches, Louis Ferdinand (1894-1961) (Louis-Ferdinand Ce´line, pseud.): Entretiens avec le Professeur Y. [fragments], undated; 51118 (Box 39.5, Folder 9)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Autographs [checks, etc.], undated; 51117 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - DDickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence, 1836-1840; 51116 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence, 1841-1842; 51115 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence, 1843; 51114 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence, 1844-1845; 51113 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence, 1846-1850; 51112 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence, 1851-1854; 51111 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence, 1855-1856; 51110 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence, 1857-1858; 51109 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence, 1859-1862; 51108 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence, 1863-1867; 51107 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence to Hindle, Rev. Joseph, 1865; 51106 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence, 1868-1869; 51105 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence [undated], 51104 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence to C.D. from family, undated; 51103 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Correspondence about C.D., undated; 51102 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): MS. Prologue to Every Man in his Humor [by Talfourd, Thomas Noon], undated; 51101 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): MS. [fragment] The Uncommercial Traveler, undated; 51100 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Dinner Invitations [October 1867], 51099 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): [family]: Dickens, Henry F., Sir, Editor, Gad's Hill Gazette, 1865; 51098 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): [family]: C.D., Jr. and the Midland R.R. Bonds [see also Oversize], undated; 51097 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): [friends]: 1 Dalby, J.W. 2 Crooke, Thomas Potter 3 Burdett-Coutts, Baroness, undated; 51096 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Memorabilia, undated; 51095 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): [about] MS. Green Leaves, by John Harrison Stonehouse, 1931; 51094 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Dickensiana: Mile End Cottage Scrapbook, undated; 51093 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): [about] Miscellaneous Article, undated; 51092 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Theatre, undated; 51091 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Dickensiana: Advertisements, undated; 51090 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Dickensiana: American Visit [1 Adv. Slip; 1 Leaflet; 1 Memo Slip; 1 Letter (2 copies)], undated; 51089 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): American Visit [Speech at City Hotel, February 18, 1842] in Brother Jonathan (2 copies), 51088 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Dickensiana: American Visit [New York], undated; 51087 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): American Visit, undated; 51086 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Dickensiana: The Boz Club, undated; 51085 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Dickensiana: The Jerrold Memorial Fund [Letters] [see also Oversize], undated; 51084 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - [Dickens, Charles (1812-1870)], undated; 51083 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Nicholas Nickleby [adaptations]: Crummleses, undated; 51082 (Box 41.5, Folder 1)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial [various by Darly], undated; 51081 (Box 41.5, Folder 2)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial [photographs and engravings of C.D.], undated; 51080 (Box 41.5, Folder 3)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial [photographs and engravings of C.D. and family], undated; 51079 (Box 41.5, Folder 4)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, David Copperfield, by F. Barnard, undated; 51078 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial [various by Browne, Hablot K.], undated; 51077 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial [various by Phiz], undated; 51076 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial [Works], undated; 51075 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial [Barnaby Rudge, miscellaneous], undated; 51074 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial [Barnaby Rudge, Yeager, engraver], undated; 51073 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, The Chimes, undated; 51072 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, A Christmas Carol, undated; 51071 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, David Copperfield, by W. H. C. Groome, undated; 51070 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Dombey, undated; 51069 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Barnaby Rudge, undated; 51068 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, David Copperfield [Dutch], undated; 51067 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Great Expectations [by J. Clayton Clark], undated; 51066 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Great Expectations [pencil drawings], undated; 51065 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Is She His Wife? [Frontispiece by F. W. Pailthorpe] [December 18, 1861], 51064 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Master Humphrey's Clock, undated; 51063 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Nicholas Nickleby, undated; 51062 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Oliver [Cruickshank drawings (great nephew, not the)], undated; 51061 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick Plates, undated; 51060 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick cheap edition, undated; 51059 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick [Darley & Furniss], undated; 51058 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick [by A. B. Frost], undated; 51057 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick [by Gibson], undated; 51056 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, various plates, undated; 51055 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick, Mulready and Miscellaneous Theatrical Productions [see also legal folders], undated; 51054 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Pickwick. Leipzig edition [43 re-engravings for 1842 Weber edition], undated; 51053 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Village Coquettes, undated; 51052 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, Various works 2, undated; 51051 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Dickensiana, clippings, undated; 51050 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): clippings, undated; 51049 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): clippings, undated; 51048 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): clippings, undated; 51047 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Dickensiana, clippings, undated; 51046 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Dickensiana, clippings & death notice, undated; 51045 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): photocopy, undated; 51044 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): theatre programs, undated; 51043 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, The Strange Gentleman, undated; 51042 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pictorial, "12 Extra Illustrations to The Pickwick Papers" [by Charles E. Block, 1921], 51041 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Photograph of Nellie Bowman as Oliver Twist, undated; 51040 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Dickens, Charles (1812-1870): Pickwick Celebrites, hand colored lithograph, undated; 51039 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Dickins, Fr., undated; 51037 (Box 46, Folder 1a)
  - Dickinson, Anna E. (Anna Elizabeth) (1842-1932), undated; 51036 (Box 46, Folder 1b)
  - Dilke, Charles Wentworth (1789-1864), undated; 51035 (Box 46, Folder 1c)
  - Disney, John (1779-1857), undated; 51034 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Disraeli, Benjamin, undated; 51033 (Box 46, Folder 2a)
  - Disraeli, Isaac, undated; 51032 (Box 46, Folder 2b)
  - Dix, Morgan (1827-1908), undated; 51031 (Box 46, Folder 3a)
  - Dixon, Arthur A., 1892-1893; 51030 (Box 46, Folder 3b)
  - Dixon, J. H., undated; 51029 (Box 46, Folder 3c)
  - Dixon, Thomas (1864-1946), undated; 51028 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Dixon, William Hepworth (1821-1879), undated; 51027 (Box 46, Folder 3e)
  - Dobson, Austin (1840-1921), undated; 51026 (Box 46, Folder 4a)
  - Dobson, Rosemary, undated; 51025 (Box 46, Folder 4b)
  - Doctorow, Edgar L., undated; 51024 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Dodd, William, undated; 51023 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Dodge, Mary Abigail (1833-1896) (Gail Hamilton, pseud.), undated; 51022 (Box 46, Folder 7a)
  - Dodge, Mary Mapes (1831-1905), undated; 51021 (Box 46, Folder 7b)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.), 1870s-1880s; undated; 51020 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.): [1889-1893, to Meehan (bookseller)], 51019 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.), 1890s; 51018 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.): [1893-1897, to Stevens, Enid], 51017 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.): MS. Poems ["The 8 Henrys"; "B.N.C."], undated; 51016 (Box 46, Folder 12a)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.): MS. "Dates of Treaties", undated; 51015 (Box 46, Folder 12b)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.): Carrolliana, undated; 51014 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (1832-1898) (Lewis Carroll, pseud.): Memorabilia [Alice photograph; doily], undated; 51013 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Dole, Nathan Haskell, undated; 51012 (Box 46.5, Folder 1a)
  - Donne, William Bodham (1807-1882), undated; 51011 (Box 46.5, Folder 1b)
  - Donnelly, Ignatius (1831-1901), undated; 51010 (Box 46.5, Folder 1c)
  - Dorman, Rushton, undated; 51009 (Box 46.5, Folder 1)
  - Dorn, Edward: Correspondence [1964-1966, to John Wieners], 51008 (Box 46.5, Folder 2)
  - Dorr, Julia C. R. (1825-1913), undated; 51007 (Box 46.5, Folder 3a)
  - Dorr, Rheta Louise (Childe), undated; 51006 (Box 46.5, Folder 3b)
  - Dorsett, A., undated; 51005 (Box 46.5, Folder 3c)
  - Dos Passos, John (1896- ), undated; 51004 (Box 46.5, Folder 4a)
  - Dos Passos, John: A.M.s.: Red, White and Blue Thanksgiving, undated; 51003 (Box 46.5, Folder 4b)
  - Dos Passos, John: A.M.s.: In Memoriam, undated; 51002 (Box 46.5, Folder 4c)
  - Doubleday, Abner (1819-1893), undated; 51001 (Box 46.5, Folder 5a)
  - Doubleday, William Elliot (1865-?), undated; 51000 (Box 46.5, Folder 5b)
  - Douglas, Alfred (Lord) (1870-1945) [Letter to Wilde], undated; 50999 (Box 46.5, Folder 6)
  - Douglas, Alfred (Lord) (1870-1945), 1917-1934; 260160 (Box 46.5, Folder 6a)
  - Douglas, Alfred (Lord) (1870-1945), 1929-1940; 260161 (Box 46.5, Folder 6b)
  - Douglas, Alfred (Lord) (1870-1945) [Transcriptions and Biographical Info], Undated; 260162 (Box 46.5, Folder 6c)
  - Douglas, Lloyd Cassel (1877-1951), undated; 50998 (Box 46.5, Folder 7a)
  - Douglas, Norman (1868-1952), undated; 50997 (Box 46.5, Folder 7b)
  - Douglas, Norman (1868-1952): [printed material], undated; 50996 (Box 46.5, Folder 8)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Andre´, Michael (Editor, Unmuzzled Ox), 1973; 50995 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Armstrong, Mike, 1966-1968; 50994 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Basak, Subimal, 1967-1975; 50993 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Beneviste, Asa and Vaughan, Paul, 1969-1973; 50992 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Berge´, Carol, 1963-1965; 50991 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Bloyek, Doug, 1966-1970; 50990 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Blomerus, Marie, 1967-1974; 50989 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Bly, Robert, 1963-1964; 50988 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Bogan, Louise, 1960-1962; 50987 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Bullock, Chris, (Editor, Bent), 1964-1966; 50986 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Choudhuri, Pradip, 1968-1975; 50985 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Cunliffe, Dave and Tina [see also Oversize], 1965-1970; 50984 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: De Loach, Allen, 1966-1973; 50983 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Dash, Tony [see also Oversize], 1968-1969; 50982 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: De Wet, Andre [South Africa], 1970-1973; 50981 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Ehrenberg, Felipe [see also Oversize], undated; 50980 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Evans, Paul, 1965-1971; 50979 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Finlay, Ian Hamilton [1964] and Fowler, Gene [1969-1970] [see also Oversize], 1964; 1969-1970; 50978 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Furnival, John, 1964-1973; 50977 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Georgakas, Dan [see also Oversize], 1967-1973; 50976 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Ginsberg, Allen [see also Oversize], 1964?-1973; 50975 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Green, Paul and Gross, Ronald, 1967-1969; 50974 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Grinberg, Miguel and Gwerda, Urban [see also Oversize], undated; 50973 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Hall, Barry; Hand, Alex [see also Oversize]; Hitchcock, George, undated; 50972 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Hollo, Anselm [see also Oversize]; Horowitz, Mike; Houe´dard, Dom Sylvester [see also Oversize], undated; 50971 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Jones, LeRoi and Kingdon, Melanie, undated; 50970 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Koch, Kenneth and Kryss, T. L., undated; 50969 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Legman, Gershon and Levertov, Denise, undated; 50968 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Levine, Stephen, (Editor, Unity Press), 1968-1974; 50967 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Levy, D. A. [see also Oversize]; Lowell, Jim [see also Oversize]; Lowenfells, Walter, undated; 50966 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Loynes, Ken (Editor, Hapt) [see also Oversize], undated; 50965 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: McCarthy, Cavan (Editor, Tlaloc), undated; 50964 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: McClure, Michael; McCord, Howard; MacDonogh, Steve; Manganotti, Donatella, undated; 50963 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Mann, Peter [see also Legal Size], undated; 50962 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Matthews, Paul (Editor, 11th Finger), undated; 50961 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Menarini, Gianni, undated; 50960 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Middleton, Fred, undated; 50959 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Morgan, Pete, undated; 50958 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Mottram, Eric [see also Legal Size], undated; 50957 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Nuttall, Jeff [see also Legal Size], undated; 50956 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Patten, Brian; Prigent, Michael, undated; 50955 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Raworth, Tom, 1963-1969; 50954 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Rothenberg, Jerome, 1963-1969; 50953 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Sanders, Ed; Saxon, Dan [see also Oversize]; Sewell, Brocard, undated; 50952 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Sigmund, R. J. [see also Levy, D. A. and Oversize], undated; 50951 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Sinclair, Iain [see also Oversize]; Sohn, Hans; Sottsass, Fernanda, undated; 50950 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Telling, Derek, (Editor, Imprint), undated; 50949 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Wagner, D.R. [see also Oversize], undated; 50948 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Wilder, Thornton, undated; 50947 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Weissner, Carl (Editor, Klact), undated; 50946 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Whalen, Philip and Williams, Jonathan, undated; 50945 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Dowden, George: Correspondence: Miscellaneous, undated; 50944 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Dowden, George: MS. Flight from America, undated; 50943 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Dowden, George: MS. Poems, undated; 50942 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Downes, George, undated; 50941 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Doyle, Arthur Conan, Sir (1859-1930), undated; 50940 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Doyle, Francis Hastings Charles, Sir (1810-1888), undated; 50939 (Box 50, Folder 3a)
  - Doyle, Richard (1824-1883), undated; 50938 (Box 50, Folder 3b)
  - Doyle, Thomas (1793-1879), undated; 50937 (Box 50, Folder 3c)
  - Draper, Amy, undated; 50936 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Dreiser, Theodore (1871-1945), 1907-1925; 50935 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Dreiser, Theodore (1871-1945): [see also Oversize], 1926-1945; 50934 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Drinkwater, John (1882-1937), undated; 50933 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Drinkwater, John (1882-1937): MS. X=O: a Night in the Trojan War, undated; 50932 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Drury, Allen: A God Against the Gods (a novel), undated; 50931 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Drummond, William Henry (1854-1907), undated; 50930 (Box 52, Folder 1a)
  - Drury, Allen Stuart, undated; 50929 (Box 52, Folder 1b)
  - Dudley, Ambrose, undated; 50928 (Box 52, Folder 1c)
  - Dumas, Alexandre (1802-1870): [see also Flat], undated; 50927 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - DuMaurier, Daphne, undated; 50926 (Box 52, Folder 3a)
  - DuMaurier, George (1834-1896), undated; 50925 (Box 52, Folder 3b)
  - Dunbar, Paul, undated; 50924 (Box 52, Folder 4a)
  - Duncan, Robert: MS. Towards an Open Universe, undated; 50923 (Box 52, Folder 4b)
  - Duncan, Todd, undated; 50922 (Box 52, Folder 4c)
  - Dunne, Finley Peter, undated; 50921 (Box 52, Folder 4)